[♪ opening theme song playing]
DAEMONS OF THE SHADOW REALM
[DERA] Come on, lady,
this is no time
to be takin' a nap.
If you don't wanna die,
you better open your eyes!
[woman groans softly]
-[DERA] Wake up!
-[woman yells]
[WOMAN] What the...
-Tadera?
-On your feet.
-Get ready to beat it.
-Wait.
What is this place?
[both chuckle]
[screams] Who are they?
So you're not their master.
I figured.
After all,
they killed your friends.
[WOMAN] They weren't my friends.
And those aren't my daemons.
Well, great.
There's a third party, then.
-[both chuckle]
-[DERA] What do they want?
And how did they
get into the clan's Lost House?
You seem to know
these stretched-out freaks.
Yes, you could say that.
Many centuries ago,
they were causing problems
in the north.
We aided a traveling monk
who wielded the power of Seal
and trapped the pair
inside Mount Yamou.
[WOMAN]
Mount... what now?
[DERA] Mount Bandai.
It was renamed after an eruption
changed its shape.
Explain. You were sealed away,
so how is it
you came to be here?
[LONG-LEG] A stroke of luck.
We have a kind new master
who recently dispelled
the miserable seal.
[LONG-ARM]
Freedom tastes so sweet
after a thousand years
of imprisonment.
Finally, our captors
stand before us.
Now you mutts are gonna pay.
[LONG-LEG] Whatever happened
to that contemptible monk?
No idea.
The last we heard,
he was on Mount Koya.
I've heard stories
about these two.
From what I remember,
the leggy one
tramples fields and crops.
Meanwhile, the other one
scoops up lake water,
causing disastrous floods.
-Such slander!
-Damn villagers.
They've been spreading
lies and nonsense
while we were suffering
in a mountain prison.
That's not
our style of mischief.
We're innocent!
The only thing we're guilty of
is eating a few people
now and then. [chuckles]
Children taste especially sweet.
[both laugh]
[LONG-LEG] I see a tender
young morsel among you. [laughs]
[LONG-ARM] He looks like
he's starting to toughen up.
But he'll still suffice.
Now, which of you
is Left and Right's master?
[woman gasps] Uh...
[LONG-LEG] Interesting.
If Left and Right are here,
does that mean
a set of twins has been born?
Be careful, Long-Arm.
One of them may wield Seal.
[LONG-ARM] We will not be
sealed away again, Long-Leg.
We must act.
Left and Right, kill them!
-[RIGHT] Uh?
-Obey my command!
What? Do you think
you can just order us around?
Huh.
At once, Master!
-If that's your wish.
-[Dera chuckles]
EPISODE 10
LONG-ARM AND LONG-LEG
[LONG-ARM] The runner
is controlling them.
We'll take our time
-devouring the boy later.
-[Yuru gasps]
[both grunting]
[LONG-ARM] Their master
will be the first to die!
-[Right grunting]
-[Long-Arm grunts]
[Right grunts]
[Long-Arm screams]
[Right grunting]
-[Long-Arm chuckles]
-[gunshots]
What's this?
He's launching
some sort of pellets at us.
[Dera grunts]
[Long-Arm laughs]
[Long-Arm yells]
They're fast.
And so slippery, it's impossible
to hold them for very long.
Conspicuous that nobody's
using Seal.
Perhaps its wielder
isn't actually here.
[LONG-LEG]
Is this meager strength
all you can muster on your own?
I was hoping you'd present
a challenge. [laughs]
[Long-Arm laughs]
Without the accursed monk
and his ability,
you're too weak.
We've craved revenge
for 1,200 years.
[LONG-ARM]
We deserve retribution. [laughs]
-Those two are terrifying!
-Dera!
Oh, Yuru.
You didn't bat an eye
at my improv.
-Nicely done.
-[YURU] Are you insane?
Why the heck
would you wanna lie
about being
Left and Right's master
in the first place?
Now those daemons
are targeting you.
Simple. I'm your guardian, kid.
Plus, your cute little sister
told me to watch your back.
Left and Right
went along with it, too.
I can protect myself, you know.
You wanna try
and fight Tenaga-Ashinaga?
You must have a death wish.
[gasps]
-[woman grunts]
-Talk fast.
Are you with the village?
Or the Kagemoris?
[grunting]
[laughs]
[DERA] You're wasting time
we don't have.
Who sent you?
It was the Kagemoris.
[woman screams]
There are different factions
within the Kagemori clan.
Who sent you after us?
[WOMAN] The second son, Asuma!
[ASUMA] The village
that produces Break and Seal
should be allowed to live on.
We mustn't reject
their very existence.
That said,
they need to be controlled
by suitable overseers.
That guy?
You might wanna know.
I was told not to harm anybody,
especially you.
Our assignment was to shadow you
and report back to him.
Damn it!
Why'd we have to go
and get dragged
into some kind of centuries old
daemon feud?
I don't wanna die!
Good news.
At the very least,
it sounds like this old bag
won't try to murder us.
Okay.
You must be a Daemon Wielder.
That much is clear.
Yeah, so?
You can help us.
Summon your daemons to fight.
Can't do it.
We all left ours behind
for the mission.
Left and Right would've noticed
other daemons in a heartbeat.
Not that it helped at all.
But we were tailing you
on our own today.
You are useless!
What was it
you were saying earlier?
This place
is a Lost House, right?
So what are we doing
still sitting around?
Let's bolt and leave
Tenaga-Ashinaga behind.
Not an option.
Those two already know
how to get in and out.
If we run, they'll follow us
with their master.
It won't work.
Right.
Then I'll hunt for whoever
is controlling them.
Daemons want
to protect their masters.
Theirs is here somewhere.
Hiding nearby, I'd guess.
Yeah, true.
And they'd probably
underestimate you
'cause they think
you're some random kid.
Right.
And I can move around freely
with minimal danger.
In fact,
since they both think
you're the one who's controlling
Left and Right,
it's likely they'll ignore me
so long as you are alive.
[DERA] That's a plan.
I'll work with Left and Right
to draw Tenaga-Ashinaga's
attention.
You look for their master.
Well, Granny? You in?
[woman whimpers]
[WOMAN] Fine.
Not like I have a choice.
[Yuru gasps] Hidden knives!
[WOMAN] Let's get this over with
so I can go home.
I have to cook dinner
for my loving husband.
[DERA]
Housewives are terrifying.
[Right grunting]
[Long-Arm laughs]
Huh? [chuckles]
[DERA]
Now to sneak into the armory.
[Dera grunts]
[Long-Arm grunting]
[Long-Arm laughs]
[Right grunts, yells]
[Dera groans]
How long do those
damn arms stretch, anyway?
Ah! The idiots
wrecked my house.
Oh, well. On the plus side,
now I've got a shortcut.
[woman panting]
[WOMAN]
Tenaga-Ashinaga's master...
Where are you? Show yourself!
I found the... [stammers]
[YURU] Sheesh. Dera said
people had died here,
but this is a lot of corpses!
The master would be
easier to track
if they were exuding bloodlust.
Think, Yuru.
Where could they be hiding?
Damn statues.
You're as tough
to break as ever.
Perhaps their master would be
easier to dispose of first!
Yes, perhaps!
How fitting to abandon them
in this place as stray daemons,
forced to rot in a Lost House
till they fade away
-into nothing!
-[gunshot]
[LONG-ARM] Uh?
No! Long-Leg!
What happened to your eye?
Was it magic?
I... I don't know!
Who did this?
[DERA] Good,
not immune to bullets.
They said themselves
they've been sealed for years,
so that means they're not
used to modern tech.
I'm more than happy
to introduce them.
I don't know what holding
a thousand-year grudge is like,
but hurt feelings mean nothing
on the other end of a gun.
You're on my turf now.
You can't do whatever you want.
[Long-Arm screams]
Long-Arm!
[Right chuckles]
[Right grunts]
[groans] I'm blind!
There's something dangerous
flying at us!
But where...
[Right grunts]
[Long-Leg grunting]
-[LEFT] Heads up!
-[Long-Leg screams]
[Right grunts]
[Long-Arm screams]
[LONG-ARM AND LONG-LEG]
Damn you!
[both scream] Damn you all!
Ah, crap.
They'll be able to see me
from that vantage.
[Long-Arm chuckles]
What's this? [laughs]
-[woman whimpers]
-[LONG-ARM] I found us a snack.
It's aged meat,
but it'll have to do.
Women are more tender than men,
and they have great flavor.
We need the sustenance to heal.
Long-Leg! You should have
the first bite! Dig in!
Ah, you're too kind.
But I will!
[woman whimpers]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I'm sure the kid I was with
would taste way better!
Ah! More importantly...
he's the twin
who will inherit Seal!
[BOTH] Huh?
[DERA] Damn old bag!
She spilled the beans!
[LONG-ARM] Come again?
[WOMAN] It's the truth!
Wouldn't it be better
to eat him?
That child you were with
is Seal?
Truly? Hmm.
[LONG-LEG]
Listen again, Long-Arm.
She said this child
may become Seal.
[LONG-ARM] And this brat
who is yet to gain
the power of Seal
is trapped in here with us.
[woman groans softly]
[WOMAN] Yeah, that's it.
Look around for the kid.
The moment
you loosen your grip,
I'll cut your
wrist tendons open
and get free!
[chuckles softly]
[woman groans]
[LONG-LEG]
As exciting as that may be,
we still need food to heal.
-[Long-Arm chuckles]
-[woman grunting]
[woman screams]
[RIGHT] Gotcha.
[LONG-ARM] Huh?
[YURU] Get your filthy hands
off that woman.
She has a family waiting
for her at home.
I'm one of the fated twins,
born to sunder night and day.
While we're at it,
I'm Left and Right's
real master.
You got a problem?
Take it up with me!
DAEMONS OF THE SHADOW REALM
You mean you are not only
one of the fated twins of lore,
but you even command
the Divine Guardians?
But the appetizer told us
you're the one to inherit Seal.
That which is yet to happen
cannot yet be a problem for us.
[LONG-ARM] Indeed!
So what should we do with him?
If we kill this morsel,
he will obtain
the power we fear.
[LONG-LEG]
I will not have a repeat
of what happened last time.
[LONG-ARM] Maybe act fast
and simply kill him twice!
[LONG-LEG] What of his mutts?
You must realize
they won't stand there
and let us end
their master's life, Long-Arm.
Yes. What of them?
Indeed.
[YURU]
Left and Right, stay there.
[RIGHT] What?
[YURU] I don't want you
to do anything until I say so.
This job falls to me.
[Right sighs softly]
[BOTH] As you command!
[laughs, grunts]
[LONG-ARM] Huh?
[Long-Arm laughs]
The stupid mutts!
They really aren't doing
anything to try and stop us!
Even the most disobedient
of dogs can be taught to "stay!“
How can he move so well?
He doesn't even have eyes
to see where he's going!
If I should lack in sight,
I may always trust Long-Arm
to act as my eyes!
And if I lack mobility,
I may always trust
Long-Leg to move me
wherever I need to go!
[Yuru yells, grunts]
[Long-Arm laughs]
Together, we are complete!
Two minds, one body!
Behold, our perfected form!
[BOTH] We are Tenaga-Ashinaga!
[Yuru grunts]
[DERA] Damn worms.
They're too big
to wriggle like that!
Why are they so fast?
I can't find a shot!
[Dera grunts]
Don't think you're
hiding from us over there!
After we're done
devouring the child,
we'll eat you next!
[Dera grunts]
[Yuru grunting]
[Long-Arm growling]
[LONG-ARM] Huh?
[Yuru gasps]
Good.
[Long-Arm growling]
[Long-Arm grunting]
[Yuru gasps]
Yuru!
Now, which part to eat first?
Should we tear off his left arm
and bleed him out?
[LONG-LEG] Perhaps we should
rip out his tongue
so he can't ask
Left and Right for help!
[Long-Leg and Long-Arm
laughing]
[Yuru grunts]
[Long-Arm gasps]
[LONG-ARM] The little brat!
Was it a lie?
Has he already claimed Seal?
Just like before...
That man lied to us in order to
draw our attention towards him!
[Long-Arm grunting]
[LONG-ARM] Was this all a trick
to catch us off-guard?
And now that we're too close
to avoid anything,
he'll Seal us away again?
[YURU] Glad to see
my ruse worked.
[Long-Arm gasps]
Your hesitation
may have only bought me
a few moments of safety.
But that's all the time
Left and Right need.
-Now go!
-[LONG-ARM] Huh?
[YURU] Do as you please!
[grunting]
[LEFT]
You have injured our master.
So now, pay the price!
[LONG-LEG] Long-Arm!
Where are you?
I can't do anything without you!
Please find me
and be my eyes again!
Why aren't you calling out?
Long-Arm!
[LONG-ARM] I'm here, Long-Leg!
I'm right here.
I need you to save me...
-[crunch]
-[Long-Arm groans]
[Right chuckles]
[RIGHT] Huh?
[LONG-LEG] Long-Arm!
Help!
[gunshot]
[Long-Leg groans]
[Dera sighs]
[LEFT] So these are
the creatures' relics.
They're steeped in power.
They'd have been gods
of some renown
had they used
their strength better.
Are you all right?
-Speak, lad!
-[Yuru coughs]
[YURU] Yeah, sure.
Great job.
Your gambit worked out!
[YURU] Hm.
[YURU] When I saw Asa use Break,
she opened a closed fist.
I kind of assumed
Seal would work
in the opposite direction.
It worked.
I scared them half to death.
Even those monsters
would be terrified
if you could seal them away
in an instant.
And I kinda get it.
I see.
When you put it like that,
it's dangerous.
This was mighty reckless
of you though, lad.
They were too much
for a human without Seal.
I wasn't trying to win.
Just serve as a distraction
for you.
So evading them was merely
the means to achieve
your true goal?
[YURU] Yeah. Like I said,
I had a job to do.
[ALL] Huh?
Found it.
This is the presence
we've felt for a while,
ever since we left
the Kagemori manor.
It was so minute,
it was hard to track.
[RIGHT] Then the humans
who were following us
were only there
to pull our focus from this?
This butterfly was
the real tail the entire time?
[WOMAN] That thing
is Asuma's daemon.
Or rather,
what you killed just now
is a piece of the whole daemon.
You haven't done
any damage to them.
Not if you only get rid of one.
[♪ closing theme song playing]
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
[YURU] You're serious?
[Ken screams]
Please, don't kill me!
[YURU]
So this is your son, Dera?
[DERA] I 100% haven't
heard that name before!
This kid isn't mine!
EPISODE 11
BIG BROTHER AND LITTLE BROTHER